...his name is gonna be Scrap Metal.
(Leonard:)Come on. Is that really necessary?
(Sheldon:)Leonard, I believe it is.
(Sheldon:)This is trash talk.
(Sheldon:)Trash talk is a traditional component
in all sporting events.
[CLEARS THROAT]
(Leonard:)Kripke...
(Sheldon:)...your robot is inferior
and it will be defeated by ours...
(Sheldon:)...because ours exceeds yours
in both design and execution.
(Sheldon:)Also, I'm given to understand
that your mother is overweight.
(Raj:)Oh, snap.
If that is a result of a glandular condition
and not gluttony...
(Sheldon:)...I withdraw that comment.
(Raj:)What difference does it make?
Fat is fat.
(Sheldon:)There are boundaries.
Tell you what, forget the SCRFLRRI.
- Let's settle this roboto a roboto.
- What do you mean?
There's no guarantee we're gonna go
against each other, so let's throw down.
You know, unless you're afraid.